A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Andrea L. Taylor FA694
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, United States International Affairs Program (USIAP), Office of the Vice President, Office Files of Andrea L. Taylor
1989-1993
Rockefeller Archive Center
Taylor, Andrea
Ford Foundation
FA694
1.31 Cubic Feet
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files and officers papers were transferred to, and accessioned by, RAC beginning in 2011. Accessions continue as necessary.
Scope and Contents
Material pertaining to the Council on Foundations as well as Taylor's trip to South Africa in 1992.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
As received.
- Council on Foundations -- Film and Video Festival, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
- Council on Foundations -- Education Committee, 1993 (Box 1)
- Council on Foundations, 1992-1993 (Box 1)
- South Africa Now, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- South Africa Trip, 1992 (Box 1)
- South Africa -- Zimbabwe Trip File, 1992 (Box 1)
- Moyo, Dr. Jonathan N., 1992 (Box 1)
- The Neiman Foundation/African-American Institute Media Conference, 1992 (Box 1)
- South Africa -- Notes, 1992 (Box 1)
- South Africa Media Program Activities, 1992 (Box 1)